A man of the claw
The VelociPastor is a action, horror, comedy film directed by Brendan Steere.
After losing his parents, a priest travels to China, where he
inherits a mysterious ability to turn into a dinosaur.
At first horrified by this new power, a prostitute convinces him to fight crime.
And ninjas.
Doug Jones / The VelociPastor, played by Gregory James Cohan.
Carol, played by Alyssa Kempinski.
Father Stewart, played by Daniel Steere.
Frankie Mermaid, played by Fernando Pacheco de Castro.
Altair, played by Aurelio Voltaire.
Wei Chang, played by Yang Jiechang.
The VelociPastor is a 2017 American comedy horror film
written, directed, and edited by Brendan Steere.
The plot follows pastor Doug Jones who becomes infected by an artifact,
resulting in him turning into a velociraptor when he becomes angry.
After screening at the B-Movie, Underground, and Trash (BUT) Film Festival on August 31, 2018, the film
received a wide release in the United States on August 13, 2019, by Wild Eye Releasing.
The film explores themes of pastor, velociraptor, ninja, b movie, dinosaur.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.